Yeah.
No.
Fuck you guys.
What?
Wait
X
Any of my joy?
Yes.
What?
She's hot.
All right,
By the end of all days.
What?
Yeah,
yeah.
What?
Yeah.
Get him.
Don't walk away here.
Uh,
buddy,
you were gone for quite a while.
We have another likes to talk that he does, but I trust he did more than talk.
Impressive.
I'm rather fond of it myself.
I've given you the skills Leonardo's given you.
The blade.
All that remains is the deed.
Where can I find Alberto?
According to my girls, he'll be attending an unveiling tonight off Morocco's latest work.
It will be held at the Santa Croce Kloster.
Watch over my mother and sister while I'm away.
Off course it as if they were my own
time.
Break something.
The idiot with a manicure.
The chemo.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
No,
Again with this, you have overstepped your bounds.
Oberto, Who are you to speak of bounds?
You who have crowned yourself Lauren Zord Immediate pain.
She pay a fair ends.
I've done no such thing.
Of course not ever innocents How convenient.
At least now we see how far your reach extends, which is to say nowhere at all.
It has proved the valuable lesson for me and my allies.
Yes, your allies.
The patsy.
Is that what this is about?
Be careful with your words.
You might attract the wrong sort of danger.
No.
Bring me your sick and wounded.
What?
Huh?
Oh,
God.
What?
Let them have a croak before.
No.
Yeah.
Good evening, favela.
Net us where?
I trust you're enjoying yourselves.
Indeed.
A nice distraction from that master business with the auditory.
And to think I won't started Javanese.
Don't blame yourself.
How could you have known?
Even I say we strike that writer's name from the record books.
Let history forget you're even existed.
Yes, if you'll excuse me for
No
a moment of your time.
Anything for you.
So tell us, how does it feel to be a hero?
Please.
I am no such thing as Gun Fallon yet it is my duty to ensure that the city of forensic remains a shining beacon of justice.
Corruption and its ilk shall find no purchase here.
So long as I am in control.
You are a treasure.
I hope Lawrence recognises that.
Yes, our great leader, Lauren.
I'll see you ladies later.
Yeah.
There you are.
I was just telling the others about the execution.
I mean, no offence, but what if they didn't know that you can rest easy friends?
I am confident that this treachery began and ended with the auditory.
What of the others?
It's
child poses, no danger.
Soft hands and an even softer hair.
You'll be caught and executed before the week is out.
Don't keep your way.
Just wanted to say hello.
Good.
Even they do.
You got in here is everything to your satisfaction.
Do you even need to ask of golf's?
Accept our thanks for this evening and for helping to keep evidence is safe.
I always had my doubts about the older daughter.
Where did the family even come from?
Who gained such with prestige in just a single generation And Children with names always making trouble.
No surprise given the company that foul
whores and thieves, I swear
in the It is clear now he sought to undermine city to overturn all we've worked so hard to be.
But thanks to you that's over there.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
You
Roberto
trusted friend of the auditory family.
According to the history books.
This guy was a saint.
He prosecuted murderers, rapists, the worst criminals.
One of the best lawyers in Italy.
He won every case in spite of the fact that he was self taught.
No.
I found a back door into the Templars database server.
I've been combing it for some kind of smoking gun.
I found it.
Apparently Alberto's family was evicted by the Medici Bank.
Roberto's be aching for revenge ever since.
And the Templars promised him support.
His father was standing in the way.
And Roberta was jealous of his influence over the Florentine government.
Two birds with one stone in it.
It looks like a Connexion to the senorita.
Is his opportunity to strike?
You would have done the same
to save the ones you love.
Yes, I would.
And I have
the door.
Only on that day I'm still here.
May
I?
You?
I want to.
Yeah.
No,
I'm home.
Wait.
You belong down below with Iraq.
I went a long way.
Yeah.
No,
wait.
Thank you,
my love.
I put these thoughts to paper in the hope that I might one day have the courage to share them with you in time.
You'll no doubt learn that I betrayed Giovanni, labelled him a traitor and sentenced him to die.
History will likely judge this to have been a matter of politics and greed.
I know that it was not hate that forced my hand but fear.
When the Medici robbed us of all we own, I found myself afraid for you, For our son, for the future.
What hope in this world for a man without proper means?
They offered me money, land and title in exchange for my collaboration.
And so this is how I came to betray my closest friend.
However unspeakable the act, it seemed necessary at the time.
And even now, looking back, I see no other way.
Yeah.
Whoa!
Poor tangled mass of flesh
One
Look, it's you.
Run!
Well done.
What is it?
Yeah,
like
huh?
I think it's best I leave here and say, Where will you go?
My Uncle Marty owns a villa near Monterey.
Joanie, you're still a wanted man.
What would you have me do that I've seen posters all across the district.
Taking them down will have the city.
Forget your face.
No doubt the Herald's also inside the public bribe them and they'll speak of other things.
Or you could hunt those who bear false witness against you.
They traded dignity for coin.
Their loss would not be mourned.
Do any of these things and you should be free to leave.
Yeah,
I've had a programme for tracking notoriety.
This little metre will help You know how far you are between notorious and inconvenient.
Yeah,
this will help.
You know, if you should watch your actions.
It'll also told your notoriety level is part of his memory or not.
Steve,
wait.
I don't Yeah, you.
Oh, Why
fresh?
What?
Okay,
yeah.
Rest in peace,
mentor.
Natto it soon.
Were you successful?
Yes.
Today.
You know what you mean they wouldn't let us leave And mother?
Oh, she hasn't spoken a single word since we left the house.
Mother will need to sort things out.
Where is Father and Federico?
Thank you.
Don't you
Some things happy?
What do you mean
no, it's impossible.
Claudia.
No, no, no, no.
I did everything I could.
No,
Lisa.
Right now, what matters is getting us all someplace safe.
But to do that I need you to stay focused.
You understand?
Good.
Will you watch over mother for me.
Then we already thank you again for everything.
Stay safe.
Stay vigilant.
I suspect the road ahead is he had long
What?
On me?
Oh God!
You could die and see me.
A wedding for your finally Come.
You don't nerve to your in your phone.
Joy are here
now.
Money
your money.
Oh
yeah.
Money.
Your money.
You!
Oh,
wow!
I heard that.
No,
Young.
What
money?
Oh
four
Treating you good.
Sorry.
Please.
I heard that
I heard
with
Give me a Me, not
one.
Fuck you!
Yeah,
Fun.
What?
No.
Sit tight.
Oh,
yeah.
With anything in front of my dress.
When you sight feast, my eyes
will meet again.
Yeah.
No
What?
Stay put
quick.
Let's do it.
It's falling.
How could this have happened to us?
I don't know.
Will we ever be back?
I don't know
what
That's it
That will happen to our house?
I don't know.
Were they were they given a proper burial?
Yes, they were.
Yeah.
Okay.
We should be close.
Fung July.
No, it's you.
How could you leave a finance?
A without saying a proper goodbye?
Did you
What do you want Vieri so many things.
A larger a lot.
So to a new states, A pretty bride.
Oh, and yes, your life.
My condolences for the
walk US gather and brothers.
What happened?
Now that there's no one left out?
I have such wonderful things in store for your mother and sister.
I grow tired of this king.
Finish him and do not spare the women.
What's so set in your face?
Not sorcery.
By still, show yourself as you wish.
You use these.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
What?
You have my thanks.
Keep the soul.
That's you.
Do I know you from somewhere?
Don't you recognise?
It's a me Mario.
Uncle Mario.
It's been too long, you know Cloud too long.
I heard what happened in Fury Agency.
Terrible.
Come, Let's get you all away from you.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Built in the 13th century by the overlords of Sienna, Monterey Goni was actively involved in the defence of Tuscany against Florentine attempts to gain more territory.
At the front of this conflict was the Audi tore, a family who became the city's rulers and protectors.
It was thie auditory who constructed Monterey Joni's famous walls, which can still be seen today.
Although standing in opposition to Florentine desires, the auditory had cordial relations with the Medici family.
Largely due to their collective Florentine roots.
Monterey Joanie successfully withstood attacks from Florence until in 15 50 for the city was betrayed.
Geovany knows Eddie, the keeper of the garrison and a Florentine exile, was allowed to return to Florence in exchange for the keys to the city.
Extraordinarily, the auditory were allowed to continue their rule of Monterey.
Joanie under Florentine leadership showing that the Medici do not forget their friends.
So tell me everything.
They executed father for treason.
Rico and Petrucci too.
They came for me.
Do you know why?
I have no answers, uncle.
Least of names taken from a man who wished me dead.
I still can't believe they're gone.
Don't worry.
We will make sense of these.
I wish I shared your optimism.
I think you will find much to like a monetary Johnny Monetary Joanie was an enemy of feet and say for now next year it will be its friend.
Year after its enemy again.
Non non.
I can't keep track.
So I've stopped trying.
These are honest, hardworking people.
Our shops may only carry simple goods, but they're well made and dependable.
There's a chapel here too.
The protest seems a nice enough fellow, but I've never been much of a believer.
Did you know the villa Auditory is almost 200 years old?
It was built by my great grandfather, a strange man who carry all kinds of secrets.
Keep your eyes open and you might discover a few of them yourself.
With all the fighting that's been going on, this place has started to get a bit rough around the edges.
I wish I could do something about it, but I just don't have the time or money to fix things up.
I guess that's life, huh?
Here we are, Gaza dodging Casa.
So what do you think?
It's most impressive, Uncle.
She's seen better days, I suppose.
Believe me, I'd have a shining again If only I had the time.
Now that you have had the tour deporting, you should go on outfit yourself.
My men in the market are expecting return here.
When you're finished and we'll begin.
Begin.
What?
I thought you'd come here to drink.
No, I'm cool.
I came here to escape UNC and I intend to take my family further still.
But what about your father?
He want you to finish his work.
What worked?
My father was a banker.
Wait, He did not tell you.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
But Chemical Beanie Giovanni.
Where to even begin.
Go and fetch the gear in the market.
You will give me time to think, but But that's that.
We'll talk more later.
Some spending money should you need it.
And if you find yourself in the depressed, I've prepared a room for you on the top floor of the villa.
If you see a fair price for quality one, you have come to the right man,
please come again.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's better for now.
But prevention is the best cure I always say.
Okay.
Normal prices for novel ways are more fit for an emperor.
And the price too much
the past, the vast web of connexions and interconnections all ruled by chance.
Or is it?
No.
So
yeah,
Don't worry.
We're only staying here for a little while.
I don't like it here.
I want to go home.
I know.
Thank you.
Date of birth 14 34 Profession KENDO Tierro Noble one of several conduct area patrolling the Tuscan countryside, Mario Auditory, played a significant role in the Battle of Angie Ari.
Alerting me, Colletto attended low to the appearance of several dust clouds over the road, which signalled a surprise advance by Melanie's troops.
Thanks to Mario, the Milanese attack was foiled in the Florentines won the battle.
Although Mario sided with Florence and Andy Ari for most of his career, he defended the interests of his hometown, Monterey Johnny, derailing Florentine attempts to seize Tuscan territory, while Margo's younger brother, Giovanni, moved to Florence in 14 54 to pursue a career in banking Mario State at the family's villa in Monterey.
Joanie stating in a letter to Giovanni that he preferred fighting like a man, too.
Filling out balance sheets
salute a uncle.
I did as you asked, and quickly, too.
In fact, now let's teach you how to fight.
No, As I said, we are leaving.
It's you.
You barely held your own against Vieri.
You won't survive a week on the road If you want to leave, so be it.
But at least do so.
Armed with the skills and knowledge necessary to defend yourself.
If not for me, For your mother and sister.
Fine.
Up to you.
You can swing a sworn to be sure.
What?
Offence alone will not carry a battle.
You must survive long enough to strike.
I will teach you how to watch.
You said my father was more than just a banker.
Yeah,
no use dancing around it.
I suppose your father was an assassination?
I told you before.
My father was a paper pusher.
No, he was born and bred to kill.
I find this difficult to believe.
One of the least you carry.
Do you think it's merely a catalogue of debts?
It holds the names of those responsible for your father's murder.
Wait, Ben.
I've taught you how to avoid your enemy's attacks.
Now you'll learn how to turn them to your advantage.
Hold this talk of assassins and Templars.
It reeks of fantasy.
Like something from a no old parchment covered in arcane writing.
Perhaps.
How did you know?
You have your father's blade?
I think you two have.
The Codex page was holding us.
Well.
Codex,
see a guide to the inner workings of the order.
Its origin Marcos and techniques are creative.
Your father believed the Codex contained a powerful secret.
Something that would change the world.
Perhaps it's why they came for him.
Assassins, Templars.
God, ex pages.
This is a lot to taking.
You need to open your mind.
It's always remember.
Nothing is true.
Everything is permitted.
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
What?
Me?
I hate these awkward moments.
So you come to me.
Bring it.
Dawn
Jen, that I lied that I made for swinging at people.
Yes.
You're making fine progress.
It's you Today.
I'm going to teach you how to position yourself in battle.
Where you stand and how you move can make all the difference.
I don't think I haven't seen you picking apart my life.
I trust you.
Believe me now.
Yes.
My father wass on the sassy.
But why the need for such secrecy?
Are you familiar with the Templars?
One of several night.
The orders form during the Crusades.
His storey teaches.
They were disbanded nearly 200 years ago in France.
Only they weren't merely pushed underground.
Where they continue various work.
What work?
The Templar seek Dominion over man.
And we The assassins are sworn to stand against them.
Was Roberto one of them?
Yes.
And the other names on my father's leased
dump?
Large as well.
That means Vieri, just like his father, from Chester.
Like the entire Potsie family.
Okay, it would explain many things.
Yeah,
so
yeah.
Yeah,
Thank you,
but
yeah,
yeah.
What?
Yeah,
me.
Well done, nipple t.
You've really come into your own.
Thank you, Uncle.
What?
All you have given me your family such is my duty and my desire.
I'm glad you had me stay good.
You've reconsidered, Lee.
We sail for Spain three days with the building.
I have given you the skills that you might be better prepared to strike against our enemies.
And if they find me, I will.
You want to leave that seal toe, throw away everything your father fuck and died for to deny your heritage.
Fine, Calm.
Avoid honorific.
Catchy point of Fortuna.
Wait!
Why is he so upset?
How can you not be?
I hear he's been harassing us ever since you first arrived to be expected, I suppose given his head
Don't go.
Where is everyone?
They write for San Gimignano will slay that snake theory.
I wish tojoin them.
You'll find what you need at the stables.
EDS.
You look at her.
I still can't get her to talk.
She spends all day and night in front of those feathers with Lucia used to collect.
She can't let him go.
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry.
She had come back to us.
I know it.
Yeah,
I may be a bit disorganised, but I do know Bring me your sick and wounded.
travel in the Renaissance was not the disgusting ordeal it is today.
Instead, it was merely terrifying.
The countryside was filled with bandits, causing most travellers to move in.
Armed groups called caravans anxious Voyager's usually sewed valuables and gold into the soles of their shoes or the lining of their jackets.
Guide's called veteran E were sometimes hired to help plot the route of the caravans and book rooms at local ends.
But those carriers were often working with the bandits, just like travel agents today.
Yeah,
okay.
Begun by Johnny Bandana, the famous architect and painter in 13 30 for this famous Gothic bell tower was incomplete When Jonah died, Andrea Paisano took over and then in 13 48 was felled by the black death in 13 59.
The tower was completed by Francesco.
Tell Andy, who deviated from John, does plan.
In his design of the upper three floors, he enlarged each floor to match the previous according to perspective.
So when seen from below, all three floors seemed to be exactly the same size.
The tower is clad with white marble from correra, red marble from CNN and green marble from Prato.
It takes exactly 414 steps to reach the top, perhaps predicting Charles Messier's discovery of the whirlpool galaxy exactly 414 years later, or perhaps not.
Two.
Constructed in 12 90 the Villa Auditory is an important mediaeval predecessor to early Renaissance architecture.
The villa's wonderful symmetry and order geometry were a revelation for its time, not only concerned with aesthetics.
Domenico Auditory Seo auditory is great.
Grandfather designed his home to double as a fortress and training ground, looking out both over the city that it protects in the Tuscan planes.
After a Florentine attack in 13 20 left, the facade damaged, the present facade was erected and a painting gallery was added to the interior.
Domenico was more than just an architect and a warrior.
He was also a skilled engineer.
Recently discovered hidden compartments and rooms with mechanisms blocking entry are several unique features of the building that make it a technological marvel, as well as an architectural one,
Yeah.